

PROFILE

Completed Bachelors of Arts in Mass communication and journalism, 2020-2023. Professionally i am a lifestyle/fashion content creator with 3 years experience of creating contents and promoting campaigns for Brands like Samsung, Lenskart, Myntra, Nykaa etc. with a collective of 59k + followers. you can find my work in the socials mentioned in this resume

REWARDS

2017 - 2019: Felicitated by ASSAM POLICE SERVICE holding Distinction in HS & HSLC

2019: Miss Icon Assam Winner 2020: KIDS Fashion show Groomer

EDUCATION

2020 - The Assam Royal Global University BA (Mass Communication & Journalism) 8.9 cgpa

2019 - Luit Valley Academy Jorhat Class XII 80.6 %

2017 - Spring Dale High School Class X 8.8 cgpa

LANGUAGES

Read: English, Assamese, Hindi, Bengali

Write: English, Hindi

Speak : English, Hindi, Assamese, Bengali

BIPASHA SARKAR

social media content creator / influencer



3rd floor,ity Tower Apartment, Thana road, Jorhat - 785001

Assam

🗾 bipashasarkar751@gmail.com

ethat_duskygirl_
https://bipashasarkar751.wixsite.com/mysite/

EXPERTISE SKILLS

Copywriting
Social Media Marketing
Creative content Creation
Scriptwriting
Editing
Blogging

EXPERIENCES

PRIYA COMMUNICATIONS

Role: Social Media Marketing Intern Period: August 2022 to September

INSIGHT BRANDCOM

Ò

Role: Project Research Intern Period: May 2022 to June 2022

THE NORTHEASTERN CHRONICLES

Role: Digital Journalist Period: August 2021 to January 2022

FIRST LADY BOUTIQUE

Role: Digital Media Marketer Period : September 2020 to June

2021